[
  {
    "id": "01",
    "question": "What is Amazon Pay used for?",
    "options": [
      "Online shopping on Amazon.in",
      "Bill payments and mobile recharges",
      "Scan and pay on any UPI QR",
      "Booking flight tickets and movie shows",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": "02",
    "question": "Is there an expiry date for using the money loaded in Amazon Pay Wallet?",
    "options": [
      "No",
      "Yes, 12 months from the date of adding",
      "Yes, 6 months from the date of adding",
      "Yes, 24 months from the date of adding"
    ],
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "id": "03",
    "question": "Can money from Amazon Pay Wallet be transferred to a bank account or another UPI user",
    "options": [
      "Yes, to both",
      "No, to both",
      "Yes, to a bank but not to another user",
      "Yes, to another user but not to a bank"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes, to both"
  },
  {
    "id": "04",
    "question": "Can you pay your utility bill using Amazon Pay?",
    "options": [
      "Yes, all utility bills",
      "No",
      "Only for water and electricity",
      "Only for broadband and DTH"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes, all utility bills"
  },
  {
    "id": "05",
    "question": "Can you use Amazon Pay to scan and pay for offline store purchases?",
    "options": [
      "Yes, can scan and Pay any UPI QR",
      "No",
      "Only in select cities",
      "Only in select stores"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes, can scan and Pay any UPI QR"
  },

  {
    "id": "06",
    "question": "How much cashback do Prime customers get for each purchase made on Amazon.in using Amazon Pay ICICI Credit Card?",
    "options": ["5%", "1%", "2%", "20%"],
    "answer": "5%"
  },

  {
    "id": "07",
    "question": "Which charities can you donate to using Amazon Pay?",
    "options": [
      "Akshaya Patra Foundation",
      "HelpAge India",
      "Milaap",
      "All of the above, and more"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above, and more"
  },

  {
    "id": "08",
    "question": "Which of these is a feature on Amazon Pay?",
    "options": [
      "Scan and Pay any UPI QR",
      "Pay to Mobile Number",
      "Bank Transfers",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },

  {
    "id": "09",
    "question": "Where can you find Amazon Pay?",
    "options": [
      "It is on your bank mobile app",
      "You have to download Amazon Pay app from Google Playstore or Apple App Store",
      "On the Amazon.in app - you already have it",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "On the Amazon.in app - you already have it"
  },

  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Which of the following merchant apps and websites accept Amazon Pay",
    "options": [
      "Swiggy",
      "BookMyShow",
      "Uber",
      "All of the above, and 20,000 more merchant apps and websites"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above, and 20,000 more merchant apps and websites"
  },

  {
    "id": "11",
    "question": "Amazon Pay Later allows you to:",
    "options": [
      "Buy now and pay next month",
      "Convert your payment into EMIs",
      "Both of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Both of the above"
  },

  {
    "id": "12",
    "question": "Which of these cards cannot be saved for payments with Amazon Pay?",
    "options": ["Credit Card", "Debit Card", "Ration Card"],
    "answer": "Ration Card"
  },

  {
    "id": "13",
    "question": "How can you add money your Amazon Pay balance?",
    "options": [
      "Net Banking",
      "UPI",
      "Load cash at door step",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },

  {
    "id": "14",
    "question": "Does Amazon Pay offer travel insurance?",
    "options": ["Yes", "No"],
    "answer": "Yes"
  },

  {
    "id": "15",
    "question": "Can you buy digital gold using Amazon Pay?",
    "options": ["Yes", "No", "Only on specific occasions"],
    "answer": "Yes"
  },

  {
    "id": "16",
    "question": "Is there a fee to maintain an Amazon Pay balance account?",
    "options": ["No", "Yes"],
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "question": "What is the convenience fee to pay bills on Amazon Pay?",
    "options": ["0%", "1%", "Depends on bill amount", "5%"],
    "answer": "0%"
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "question": "How much cashback do customers get for bill payments using Amazon Pay ICICI Credit Card?",
    "options": ["Unlimited 2%", "0%", "7.5%", "20%"],
    "answer": "Unlimited 2%"
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "question": "What is the maximum amount of cash that can be loaded at your door step in Amazon Pay Wallet per month?",
    "options": ["50,000", "5,100", "999", "Unlimited"],
    "answer": "50,000"
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "question": "What can Amazon Pay Gift Card be used for?",
    "options": [
      "Shopping from 15+ Cr products on Amazon.in",
      "Pay on 20,000+ merchants websites & apps",
      "Travel & movie ticket bookings",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  }
]
